Register of the Norwood F. Allman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1943-1987
  - Taylor, Lemuel (Folder 54)
  - Taylor, William H. (Folder 55)
  - Tenberge, Jacobus (Folder 56)
  - Teng, Chung-ho (Folder 57)
  - Teng, Hsiao-ping (Folder 58)
  - Teng, Ying-chao (Folder 59)
  - Tennien, Mark (Folder 60)
  - Tesmenitsky, L. A. (Folder 61)
  - Thai diplomats, military and public figures, statesmen (Folder 62)
  - Thakur, B. T. (Folder 63)
  - Thant, U. (Folder 64)
  - Thein Maung (Folder 65)
  - Thien Pe (Folder 66)
  - Thomas, Richard (Folder 67)
  - Thompson, Virginia, "Burma and Two Chinas," Foreign Policy Bulletin, Vol. 32, No., 17, May 15, 1953 (Folder 68)
  - Tieng, Sing (Folder 69)
  - Tilaka, Dang (Folder 70)
  - Ting, Ling (Folder 71)
  - Tjong, Hoen-nji (Folder 72)
  - Tofte, Hans V. (Folder 73)
  - Todd, William Lewis (Folder 74)
  - Togo, Shigenori (Folder 75)
  - Tojo, Eiki (Folder 76)
  - Tomoyasu, Hitoshi (Folder 76A)
  - Tong, Hollington (Folder 77)
  - Toyama, Mitsuru (Folder 78)
  - Toyoda, Teijiro (Folder 79)
  - Toyodas, Sayemu (Folder 80)
  - Tsai, Chang (Folder 81)
  - Tsai, Ping-fan (Folder 82)
  - Tsao, L. E. (Folder 83)
  - Tse, Stephen (Folder 84)
  - Tseng, T. C. (Folder 85)
  - Tsing, Di-tsin (Folder 86)
  - Tsou, Lu (Folder 87)
  - Tsou, Lu-te (Folder 88)
  - Tsubogami, Teiji (Folder 89)
  - Tsukada, Osamu (Folder 90)
  - Tsurumi, K. (Folder 91)
  - Tu, Y. C. (Folder 92)
  - Tularaksa, Sanguan (Folder 93)
  - Tung, Chen-tang (Folder 94)
  - Tung, Chien-sen (Folder 95)
  - Tung, Chi-ling (Folder 96)
  - Tung, Jack (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tung, L. S. (Folder 2)
  - Tung, Lung-san (Folder 3)
  - Tung, Shou-i (Folder 4)
  - Tung, Tran Van (Folder 5)
  - Twanmoh, Joseph K. (Folder 6)
  - Twomy, Father (Folder 7)
  - Uba Muang (Folder 8)
  - Uchida, Ashinari (Folder 9)
  - Uchida, Ryohei (Folder 10)
  - Uchiyama, Yoshio (Folder 11)
  - Ueno, Kanichiro (Folder 12)
  - Ulrich, Basil von (Folder 13)
  - Umezu, Yoshijiro (Folder 14)
  - United Chemical Industries, Federal Inc. (Folder 15)
  - United Industries, Inc. (Folder 16)
  - U.S. Office of Strategic Services
    - General (Folder 17)
    - "Japanese Espionage,", 1943 (Folder 18)
  - Ushijima, Mitsuru (Folder 19)
  - Ushiroku, Jun (Folder 20)
  - Uyeda, Kenkichi (Folder 21)
  - Van Oyen, L. H. (Folder 22)
  - Vargas, Jorge (Folder 23)
  - Varavarn, Sakol (Folder 24)
  - Varavarn, Vanvaidyakara (Folder 25)
  - Vareyodha, Luang (Folder 26)
  - Varnvaidyakara, Prince (Folder 27)
  - Vaught, Arnold (Folder 28)
  - Vegh, Jeno (Folder 29)
  - Veterans of O.S.S. Organizationu (Folder 30)
  - Vichien Yongchaiyudh, Lt. (Folder 31)
  - Vijitvadtakarn, Vijit (Folder 32)
  - Villamor, Jesus (Folder 33)
  - Vincent, John C. (Folder 34)
  - Vines, C. C. (Folder 35)
  - Vira Virayota, General (Folder 36)
  - Wainright, Jonathan (Folder 37)
  - Waldron, M. (Folder 38)
  - Wallace, Henry (Folder 39)
  - Walsh, James E. (Folder 40)
  - Walsh, Vincent P. (Folder 41)
  - Wan, Chao-chih (Folder 42)
  - Wan, Fu-lin (Folder 43)
  - Wang, C. F. (Folder 44)
  - Wang, C. S. (Folder 45)
  - Wang, C. T. (Folder 46)
  - Wang, Chen-hua (Folder 47)
  - Wang, Chia-hsiang (Folder 48)
  - Wang, Chi-chuan (Folder 49)
  - Wang, Chih-hsiang (Folder 50)
  - Wang, Ju-mei (Folder 51)
  - Wang, Sheng-chuan (Folder 52)
  - Wang, Shu-ming (Folder 53)
  - Wang, Y. Chu (Folder 54)
  - Wang, Yin Pao (Folder 55)
  - Wang, Tieh-yai (Folder 56)
  - Ward, Ralph A. (Folder 57)
  - Warner-Hudnut Fed., Inc. (Folder 58)
  - Watson, Williams C. (Folder 59)
  - Wei, H. R. (Folder 60)
  - Wei, Joseph (Folder 61)
  - Wei, Lott (Folder 62)
  - Wei, T. F. (Folder 63)
  - Wei, T. F. (Charlie) (Folder 64)
  - Wei, Tao Ming (Folder 65)
  - Wei, Ta-wei (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Weir, Ernest (Folder 2)
  - Wen, Wen-ho (Folder 3)
  - Wen, Ying H. (Folder 4)
  - Wen, Ying-shing (Folder 5)
  - Wendler, Ernst (Folder 6)
  - Wendt, W. (Folder 7)
  - Weng, Chao-yuan (Folder 8)
  - Weng, Hsing-ching (Folder 9)
  - Weng, Wen-hao (Folder 10)
  - Wennecker, Vice Admiral (Folder 11)
  - Werner, Mr. (Folder 12)
  - Wetzel, A. F. (Folder 13)
  - Wheaton, Louis A. (Folder 14)
  - Whitacre, Dr. (Folder 15)
  - White, Harry Dexter (Folder 16)
  - White, John W. (Folder 17)
  - White, Theodore (Folder 18)
  - Whiteing, Percy (Folder 19)
  - Whittaker, E. G. (Folder 20)
  - Who's Who in China Project (Folder 21)
  - Whyte, Hartley (Folder 22)
  - Wiedemann, Fritz (Folder 23)
  - Wilbur, C. Martin (Folder 24)
  - Wilkins, Ford (Folder 25)
  - Willauer, Whiting (Folder 26)
  - Willcox, Henry (Folder 27)
  - William, Maurice (Folder 28)
  - Williams, Frederick V. (Folder 29)
  - Williams, J. C. (Folder 30)
  - Williams, Mrs. O. L. (Folder 31)
  - Wilmott, L. E. (Folder 32)
  - Wilson, John (Folder 33)
  - Wilson, Mrs. (Folder 34)
  - Winnington, Alan (Folder 35)
  - Wirsing, Dr. (Folder 36)
  - Witherspoon, Maurice (Folder 37)
  - Witt, Eric G. (Folder 38)
  - Wohlthat, Helmut (Folder 39)
  - Wolf, Popper, Ross & Wolf (Folder 40)
  - Wolferz, Louis (Folder 41)
  - Wolferz, Mrs. (Folder 42)
  - Wolff, T. J. (Folder 43)
  - Wong, Albert (Folder 44)
  - Wong, Allen (Folder 45)
  - Wong, Amos (Folder 46)
  - Wong, Anna (Folder 47)
  - Wong, C. C. (Folder 48)
  - Wong, George (Folder 49)
  - Wong, H. (Folder 50)
  - Wong, H. Dan (Folder 51)
  - Wong, Henry (Folder 52)
  - Wong, Jennings (Folder 53)
  - Wong, Joseph (Folder 54)
  - Wong, L. P. (Folder 55)
  - Wong, Martin (Folder 56)
  - Wong, N. K. (Folder 57)
  - Wong, Phoebe (Folder 58)
  - Wong, R. (Folder 59)
  - Wong, S. J. (Folder 60)
  - Wong, Yan Dong (Folder 61)
  - Woo, Kya-tang (Folder 62)
  - Woodhead, George (Folder 63)
  - Woodhead, H. G. W. (Folder 64)
  - Woodman, Dorothy (Folder 65)
  - Wousaofong (Folder 66)
  - Wu, Bill (Folder 67)
  - Wu, Chien-shiung (Folder 68)
  - Wu, Chih-hui (Folder 69)
  - Wu, John C. (Folder 70)
  - Wu, K. C. (Folder 71)
  - Wu, Nan-ju (Folder 72)
  - Wu, Te-chen (Folder 73)
  - Wu, Yao-tsung (Folder 74)
  - Wu, Yi-fang (Folder 75)
  - Wu, Ying-fang (Folder 76)
  - Wu, Yu-chang (Folder 77)
  - Wu, Yun-chu (Folder 78)
  - Yamada, Kisanosuke (Folder 79)
  - Yamada, Otozo (Folder 80)
  - Yamamoto, Isoroku (Folder 81)
  - Yamashita, Kemasabuto (Folder 82)
  - Yamashita, Tomoyuki (Folder 83)
  - Yamawaki, Masataka (Folder 84)
  - Yang, Chi-tseng (Folder 85)
  - Yang, Fan (Folder 86)
  - Yang, Chih-hsiung (Folder 87)
  - Yang, Kuan-Pei (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Yang, Yin (Folder 2)
  - Yannoulatos, Paul (Folder 3)
  - Yano, Muraji (Folder 4)
  - Yao, Yung-li (Folder 5)
  - Yaung, Melanie (Folder 6)
  - Yeh, Chien-ying (Folder 7)
  - Yeh, George (Folder 8)
  - Yen, Chia-kan (Folder 9)
  - Yen, Chu-tsang (Hsiao-feng) (Folder 10)
  - Yen, Sheng (Folder 11)
  - Yodha, Luang (Folder 12)
  - Yodhi, Luang (Folder 13)
  - Yokoyama, Isamu (Folder 14)
  - Yomaraj, Chao (Folder 15)
  - Yone, Edward (Folder 16)
  - Yonai, Mitsumasa (Folder 17)
  - Yoshida, Zengo (Folder 18)
  - Yoshino, Shinji (Folder 19)
  - Yoshizawa, Kenkichi (Folder 20)
  - Young, John (Folder 21)
  - Young, Pat (Folder 22)
  - Young, Paul B. (Folder 23)
  - Younger, Kenneth (Folder 24)
  - Yu, Hon Mow (Folder 25)
  - Yu, Ta-wei (Folder 26)
  - Yu Tung Navigation Corporation (Folder 27)
  - Yuan, Frances (Folder 28)
  - Yuan, Jack (Folder 29)
  - Yuan, L. Z. (Folder 30)
  - Yuan, Yi-chuan (Folder 31)
  - Yuasa, Kurahei (Folder 32)
  - Yui, O. K. (Folder 33)
  - Yuki, Seitaro (Folder 34)
  - Yuki, Toyotaro (Folder 35)
  - Yulo, Jose (Folder 36)
  - Yusawa, Michio (Folder 37)
  - Zeltzer, Raphael (Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 39-40)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1929-1987
  - 12 prints of Norwood Allman alone and with others (Envelope A)
  - 8 prints of the Norwood Allman and other members of the Shanghai Volunteer Corps (Envelope B)
  - 7 prints of N. Allman and others on horseback and on foot at the Shanghai Race Course (Envelope C)
  - 4 prints of N. Allman and others on horseback in the countryside (Envelope D)
- DECLASSIFIED U.S. GOVERNMENT RECORDS, circa 1942-1950
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Available as PDF files. The PDF files are page images, so full-text search is not possible. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder by date of creation.
  - 2010 release of records, circa 1942-1950 (Reading room Workstation)
  - 2017 release of records, circa 1942-1950 (Reading room Workstation)